ilividlive.com 2016-12-07

# Privacy Policy | inMind – The Best of the Internet

INMIND INC ("InMind") takes your privacy very seriously. Please read the following to learn more about InMind's Privacy Policy ("Policy"). This Policy details how InMind receives, collects and uses information in connection with their website located at InMind.com and software provided on the InMind.com website (the website and software collectively referred to herein as "Site").

Collection and Use of Information

InMind does not automatically collect any personally identifiable information, such as names, e-mail, age, gender, address, telephone numbers, login names and passwords or other self-identifying information ("Personal Information"). InMind may request that a user provide an e-mail address if such user wishes to be contacted regarding any offers, updates, newsletters and service related announcements. If a user provides an e-mail address to InMind, such user authorizes InMind to send user communications.

InMind may use cookies on the Site. Cookies are pieces of information that a website transfers to an individual's hard drive for record-keeping purposes. Cookies make web-surfing easier by saving preferences and browsing patterns while you are at InMind's Site. Cookies may be used to analyze Site usage, improve content, customize the Site's content and layout and for other customer service purposes. InMind's use of cookies is in no way linked to any Personal Information.

InMind may automatically receive and record certain non-personally identifiable information on its server logs from your browser, including your IP address, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), cookie information, and the webpage that a user visits. InMind collects non-personally identifiable information for general purposes, including but not limited to analyzing trends, administering the site, tracking user movements, conducting research, and providing anonymous reporting to internal and external clients. InMind will not link any Personal Information, including e-mail addresses, with aggregate data of its users.

Sharing and Disclosure of Information

InMind does not rent, sell, or share any information about the user with any third-parties. InMind may disclose your Personal Information if InMind believes such action is necessary to: (a) comply with the law or legal process served on InMind; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of InMind (including the enforcement of our agreements); or (c) act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of InMind services or members of the public.

Children's Privacy

Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. We operate our website in compliance with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA). We never knowingly collect or maintain information at or on our website from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is directed at or structured to attract anyone under 13. Visitors younger than 13 years of age may NOT use the InMind website and software and must LEAVE immediately.

Security

InMind takes reasonable precaution to protect Personal Information from misuse, loss and unauthorized access. Although InMind cannot guarantee that Personal Information will not be subject to unauthorized access, InMind has physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to protect the Personal Information. Personal Information is protected by secured networks and access is limited to a few authorized employees and personnel. However, no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however.

Business Transitions

In the event that InMind goes through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, Personal Information will likely be among the assets transferred. InMind will post a notice on this website of any such change in ownership or control of the Personal Information InMind may have prior to such transfer.

Changes to Policy

From time to time, InMind may revise this Policy. InMind will post the revised Policy on the Site, so that users can always be aware of what information InMind collects, how the information is used and under what circumstances such information may be disclosed.

Change or Removal of Information

If a user's e-mail address changes, a user may correct such information by sending an e-mail to [support@inmind.com](mailto:support@inmind.com) with the request or by contacting us by telephone or postal mail at the contact information listed below.

If a user no longer wishes to receive e-mail communication from InMind, such as offers, updates and newsletters, a user may opt-out of receiving such communications by following the instructions included in each newsletter or communication. In addition, a user can remove their e-mail address at any time by sending an e-mail with the subject line of OPT-OUT to [support@inmind.com](mailto:support@inmind.com)
